Guide to the Cartoon art collection, 1926-1988.
Cartoon art collection
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cartoon art collection, 1926-1988.
8030
ca. 30 cubic feet
Artwork, proofs, and releases.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Original illustrations and prepress proofs of cartoon art. Comic strips represented include the Berrys, Bi-focals, the Bungle Family, Cicero's Cat, the Flintstones, Grafitti, Gunther, Heathcliff, the Jackson Twins, Joe Palooka, Mickey Finn, Mutt and Jeff, Sal A. Mander, Sparky Watts, Stoker, This Funny World, and Yogi Bear. Also includes releases compiled by McNaught Syndicate.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Original illustrations and prepress proofs of cartoon art. Comic strips represented include the Berrys, Bi-focals, the Bungle Family, Cicero's Cat, the Flintstones, Grafitti, Gunther, Heathcliff, the Jackson Twins, Joe Palooka, Mickey Finn, Mutt and Jeff, Sal A. Mander, Sparky Watts, Stoker, This Funny World, and Yogi Bear. Also includes releases compiled by McNaught Syndicate.
SUBJECTS
Names:
McNaught Syndicate.
Subjects:
Comic books, strips, etc.; Newspapers -- Sections, columns, etc. -- Comics.; Comic books, strips, etc.; Newspapers -- Sections, columns, etc. -- Comics
Form and Genre Terms:
Illustrations
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Cartoon Art, Prints, and Releases
Subseries Ia. The Berrys by Carl Grubert
Subseries Ib. Bi-Focals by Ruth Marcus
Subseries Ic. The Bungle Family by HJ Tuthill
Subseries Id. Cicero's Cat by Al Smith
Subseries Ie. Dixie Dugan by McEvoy and Striebel
Subseries If. The Flintstones by Hanna-Barbera
Subseries Ig. Graffiti by Bill Leary
Subseries Ih. Gunther by John Roman
Subseries Ii. Heathcliff by George Gately
Subseries Ij. The Jackson Twins by Dick Brooks
Subseries Ik. Joe Palooka by Tony DiPreta
Subseries Il. Mickey Finn by MS Weiss
Subseries Im. Mutt and Jeff by Al Smith
Subseries Im. Mutt and Jeff by Al Smith
Subseries In. Red Ryder by Fred Harman
Subseries Io. Sal A. Mander by Fred Harman
Subseries Ip. Sparky Watts by Boody Rogers
Subseries Iq. Stoker by Henry Boltinoff
Subseries Ir. This Funny World by various artists, listed alphabetically
Subseries Is. Yogi Bear by Hanna-Barbera
Subseries It. Miscellaneous comics
Series II. Political Cartoons
Series III. Miscellaneous Promotional Materials
Series IV. McNaught Files
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Cartoon Art, Prints, and Releases
  - Subseries Ia. The Berrys by Carl Grubert
    - 45 original drawings. Originals of The Berrys weekly strip from 1945, unsigned., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 48 original drawings., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Carl Grubert begins signing his name to the strips on August 8, 1946.
    - The Berrys colored proofs, 1946 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      Colored proofs of The Berrys weekly strip from 1946, small size, some are undated, but all are filed in order by date by being matched with the originals.
    - The Berrys colored proofs, ca. 1946 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      Colored proofs of The Berrys weekly strip, large size, undated but from August-September 1946 based on originals.
  - Subseries Ib. Bi-Focals by Ruth Marcus
    - Bi-Focals original drawings, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      24 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Bi-Focals original drawings, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      9 original drawings, Sunday strips, some hand-colored by artist.
    - Bi-Focals original drawings, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      4 original drawings, Sunday strips, some hand-colored by artist
    - Bi-Focals miscellaneous colored sheet (Box 2, Folder 4)
      1 original.
  - Subseries Ic. The Bungle Family by HJ Tuthill
    - The Bungle Family list, 1936-1937 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      List of strips for 1936 on verso of releases of Look Here column by Charles B. Driscoll, 1938.
    - The Bungle Family proofs, 1938-1939 (Box 34, Folder 2)
      Proofs of full-page weekly strips, with list of strips on verso of releases of Look Here column by Charles B. Driscoll, 1938.
    - The Bungle Family proofs, 1939-1942 (Box 34, Folder 3-4)
      Proofs of half-page weekly strips.
  - Subseries Id. Cicero's Cat by Al Smith
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, March, April 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      2 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, November-December, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      8 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, February-December, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      39 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, February-December, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      47 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      52 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Cicero's Cat originals, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      56 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat drawings, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      38 original drawings.
    - Cicero's Cat original drawings, January-November, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      23 original drawings.
  - Subseries Ie. Dixie Dugan by McEvoy and Striebel
    - Dixie Dugan dailies releases, 1961-1964 (Box 45, Folder 18-21)
    - Dixie Dugan Sundays releases, 1958-1960 (Box 46, Folder 1-3)
    - Dixie Dugan daily releases, 1958-1960 (Box 46, Folder 4-5)
    - Dixie Dugan releases, 1955-1960 (Box 46, Folder 6-12)
    - Dixie Dugan releases, 1961-1966 (Box 47, Folder 1-6)
  - Subseries If. The Flintstones by Hanna-Barbera
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      1 original drawing, daily strip.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      35 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      10 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      154 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, January-May, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      96 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, May-August, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      93 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, September-December, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      95 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, January-April, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - The Flintstones original drawings, April-August, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
      97 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, August-December, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
      90 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, January-April, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - The Flintstones original drawings, February-August, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 5)
      91 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, August-December, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      86 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstonesoriginal drawings, January-February, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 7)
      25 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstonesoriginal drawings, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 8)
      5 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      21 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
      34 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      40 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, January-September, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      32 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, March, December 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
      6 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 3)
      51 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones original drawings, January-March, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 4)
      8 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones copies, March, November-December, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 1)
      Black and white copies of Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones copies, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - The Flintstones copies, January-March, 1981 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - The Flintstones black and white proofs, August, 1977 (Box 36, Folder 1)
      Black and white proofs of Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones black and white proofs, 1978 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - The Flintstones black and white proofs, October, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Black and white proofs of Sunday strips, large.
    - The Flintstones black and white proofs, January-September, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - The Flintstones blue proofs, May-December, 1978-1979 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      Blue proofs of Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones colored strips, December, 1976-1877 (Box 33, Folder 4)
      Colored Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones colored strips, 1978 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - The Flintstones coloring diagrams, March, December, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 3)
      Coloring diagrams for Sunday strips.
    - The Flintstones coloring diagrams, January-March, 1981 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Yogi Bear and The Flintstones film proofs (Box 39, Folder 6)
      3 sheets, Yogi Bear and Flintstones on same sheet.
    - The Flintstones negatives, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Folder 1-4)
    - The Flintstones negatives, 1978-1981 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
    - The Flintstones Sunday releases, 1962-1964 (Box 47, Folder 18-20)
    - The Flintstones Sunday releases, 1966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - The Flintstones daily and Sunday releases, 1965, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2-4)
    - The Flintstones daily releases, 1961-1966 (Box 48, Folder 5-7)
    - The Flintstones, colored, 1963-1965 (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - The Flintstones, Sunday releases, 1968-1972 (Box 48, Folder 9-12)
    - The Flintstones, dailies and Sunday releases, 1969, 1973-1974 (Box 48, Folder 13-15)
    - The Flintstones, promos, 1978-1979 (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - The Flintstones, daily releases, 1968, 1970-1972, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 1-5)
  - Subseries Ig. Graffiti by Bill Leary
    - Graffiti, ca. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      62 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, includes paste-up of similar strip called Bumper Sticker, set of numbered backgrounds for Graffiti, undated panels of Graffiti, some of which may be from 1968 and before based on topical references to political figures, Chicago convention, election, etc.
    - Graffiti, ca. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      60 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, includes paste-up of similar strip called Bumper Sticker, set of numbered backgrounds for Graffiti, undated panels of Graffiti, some of which may be from 1968 and before based on topical references to political figures, Chicago convention, election, etc.
    - Graffiti, ca. 1968 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Graffiti, May-August, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      35 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn
    - Graffiti, September-October, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      38 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, October-December, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      67 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, January-February, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      57 326 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, March-April, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
      54 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, May-June, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 9)
      55 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, July-August, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      56 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, September-October, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Graffiti, November-December, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      50 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, January-February, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Graffiti, March-April, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti, May-June, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      53 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, July-August, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      52 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, September-October, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      39 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, November-December, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      40 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, January-April, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 4)
      79 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, May-June, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      51 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, July-September, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      61 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, September-October, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      24 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, October, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      12 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, October-November, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      9 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Graffiti (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Graffiti, November-December, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      36 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, January, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      7 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, multiple strips mounted on heavy cardboard.
    - Graffiti, January, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 12)
      9 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, multiple strips mounted on heavy cardboard.
    - Graffiti (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Graffiti, January-March, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      59 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, April, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti, April-June, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Graffiti, June-July, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      18 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, multiple strips mounted on heavy cardboard.
    - Graffiti, July-November, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      125 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - 11 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, multiple strips mounted on heavy cardboard., November-December, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - 24 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn., December, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Graffiti, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 2)
      25 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn, multiple strips mounted on heavy cardboard.
    - Graffiti, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      72 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 4)
      75 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
      98 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      78 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      69 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      89 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Graffiti, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Graffiti, 1976 (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Graffiti, January-March, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Graffiti, April-June, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 13)
      76 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, July-September, 1977 (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti, October-December, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Graffiti, January-April, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      99 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, May-August, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      106 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, September-December, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      104 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, January-April, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      103 single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, May-August, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Graffiti, September-December, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Graffiti, January-April, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      104 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, May-August, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 9)
      105 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, September-December, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Graffiti, January-April1981 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      103 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, May-September, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      110 original single panel daily strips, many written not drawn.
    - Graffiti, releases, 1969-1970 (Box 49, Folder 6-9)
    - Graffiti, releases, 1971-1972 (Box 49, Folder 10-13)
    - Graffiti, releases, 1976 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Graffiti, releases, 1979-1980 (Box 49, Folder 15-16)
  - Subseries Ih. Gunther by John Roman
    - Gunther original drawings, March-September, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 1)
      172 original drawings.
  - Subseries Ii. Heathcliff by George Gately
    - Heathcliff original drawings, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 1)
      24 original drawings, single panel originals.
    - Heathcliff original drawings, 1976-1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
      10 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - Healthcliff promos, ca. 1980 (Box 36, Folder 6)
      Miscellaneous promotional materials for Heathcliff.
    - Heathcliff coloring diagrams, 1979 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      Copies of Sunday strips with numbered instructions for coloring.
    - Heathcliff newsprint proofs, 1977-1978 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Heathcliff black and white copies, 1976-1982 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Heathcliff bluelines, 1979-1980 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      Blue proofs
    - Heathcliff color copies, 1980 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Heathcliff Sunday releases, 1980 (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Heathcliff dailies, 1976-1981 (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Heathcliff negatives, 1981 (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
      4 files of negatives for Sunday strips, filed according to size.
    - Heathcliff negatives, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Heathcliff negatives, 1981 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Subseries Ij. The Jackson Twins by Dick Brooks
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, August-September, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 1)
      12 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, February-September, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      61 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, September-December, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      64 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, December, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      26 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, January-March, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 1)
      57 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, April-June, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 2)
      53 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, July-August, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, September-October, 1978 (Box 20, Folder 4)
      52 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, November-December, 1978 (Box 79, Folder 1)
      58 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, January-February, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 2)
      51 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, March-August, 1979 (Box 79, Folder 3)
      33 original drawings, daily strips.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1)
      28 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Jackson Twins, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
      1 colored proof, Sunday strip.
    - The Jackson Twins original drawings, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 3)
      37 original drawings, Sunday strips.
    - The Jackson Twins, daily releases, 1955, 1957-1960 (Box 49, Folder 17-20)
    - The Jackson Twins, daily releases, 1961-1964, 1966 (Box 50, Folder 1-3)
    - The Jackson Twins, Sunday releases, 1958, 1960-1961, 1964 (Box 50, Folder 4-7)
    - The Jackson Twins, daily and Sunday releases, 1968-1973 (Box 50, Folder 8-13)
  - Subseries Ik. Joe Palooka by Tony DiPreta
    - Joe Palooka daily releases, 1949, 1956, 1981 (Box 56, Folder 18-20)
    - Joe Palooka original drawings (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, August-September, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, July, October-December, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 3)
      135 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, January-February, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 4)
      48 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, March-July, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      112 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, August-December, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 6)
      130 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, January-June, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 1)
      154 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, July-December, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 2)
      156 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, January-June, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 3)
      155 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, July-December, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 4)
      114 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, January-May, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 1)
      96 original drawings of daily strip.
    - Joe Palooka original drawings, June-September, 1981 (Box 80, Folder 2)
      77 original drawings of daily strip.
  - Subseries Il. Mickey Finn by MS Weiss
    - Mickey Finn copies, April-December, 1942; 1943 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      Copies of weekly releases, not originals.
    - Mickey Finn copies, 1944-1946 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Mickey Finn copies, 1947-1949 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Mickey Finn original drawings, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
      20 original drawings, featuring Uncle Phil, Sunday strips.
    - Mickey Finn original drawings, 1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Mickey Finn original drawings, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
      41 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Mickey Finn original drawings, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 4)
      6 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Mickey Finn weekly releases, 1978 (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - Mickey Finn releases, 1949 (Box 65, Folder 50)
  - Subseries Im. Mutt and Jeff by Al Smith
    - Mutt and Jeff Sunday releases, 1971-1972 (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - Mutt and Jeff daily releases, 1971-1973, 1976, 1979 (Box 56, Folder 24-25)
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
      3 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, July-October, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 3)
      62 original drawings, daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, October-December, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 5)
      99 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 6)
      71 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 1)
      60 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 2)
      90 original daily strips, phone messages from Bill Olsen, Helena Norman, and Bruce Frazer written on back of March 23 strip.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 3)
      63 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
      50 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 1)
      78 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 3)
      79 original daily strips.
    - Mutt and Jeff original drawings, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      73 original daily strips.